(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Tiffany loved working with kids.
She wanted to be a kindergarten teacher when
she grew up.
She decided to volunteer now to prepare her.
She volunteered as a tutor.
She would teach young children.
She focused on English.
She taught kids how to read and write.
Volunteering allowed her to work with kids.
She loved talking to them.
She hoped that she would inspire them.
The kids she taught were of all ages.
She especially liked working with young kids.
This week, she was teaching them about essays.
She taught them the format.
She had each of the kids write one
essay about their life.
She felt prepared for her future career.